latestdeals.co.uk 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | LatestDeals.co.uk

**What information is being collected?**

If you sign up as a member to Latest Deals we will store your e-mail address and chosen username so we can get in touch. If you register via Facebook you'll have an option to choose what information you provide us. By default, Facebook sends us what is referred to as your "public profile" information. This can include your email address, full name, profile picture, gender and age range. Whilst signing up you can choose what information is shared with us and opt out if you would prefer.

We also store your IP address. We do this to help prevent abuse of the Latest Deals community and it's [guidelines](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/guidelines). For example, we may use the IP address to detect retailers who sign up for multiple accounts to try and unscrupulously promote their own services.

For the purpose of creating new features and functionality in the future (e.g. cash back and a personalised deals feed) we store information about some purchases made through the Latest Deals website. This may include products purchased, amount spent and other associated information.

If you choose to sign up for our WhatsApp notifications your mobile number is stored so that we can send you messages. Similarly, if you choose to sign up for our Facebook Messenger notifications, your public Facebook profile information may be stored. For clarity: you have to actively opt-in to these services.

 **Who is collecting the data and who is it shared with?**

We (Latest Deals Limited) hold your data and do not share it with any third parties other than set out below:

  * Our website uses Google Analytics to analyse how users interact with the site. This is fairly standard practice amongst websites and we assure you nothing untoward is going on! It helps us keep track of the number of visitors to Latest Deals and spot popular deals and trends. You can read more about Google Analytics and the what/how/why at their website, [here](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/go?link=5abd0b70cf4cdd03d960db73). We anonymise your IP address before sending it to Google Analytics.
  * We use a service called [MailChimp](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/go?link=592f705cedba831afa13f6aa) to manage our email newsletter subscriptions. We share your email address and, if you provided it to us, your full name with MailChimp. This allows us to send you personalised emails.
  * If you sign up to our WhatsApp notifications, your mobile number and any interactions with us via WhatsApp are handled and stored by a third party service called [MessengerPeople](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/go?link=5ba20c1ad4a2e63dd9bf3d31).
  * If you sign up for our Facebook Messenger notifications, your public Facebook profile information will be handled and stored by a third party service called [ManyChat](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/go?link=5ba20c1ad4a2e63dd9bf3d33).

 **Why is the data collected?**

We ask for your email address so that we can get in touch with you. As outlined above, your IP address is stored to help prevent the abuse of Latest Deals. Any other information is used to help improve Latest Deals and tailor our content to our visitors.

For full details of why data is collected by the third party services we use, please review their privacy policies from the website links above.

 **Getting a copy of your personal information**

You're welcome to [contact us](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/contact) if you would like a copy of your personal information that we hold.

 **What if my personal information is incorrect?**

If you believe any of the information that we hold (e.g. your email address) is incorrect you can [contact us](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/contact) to let us know and we'll make sure it's up to date.

 **How can I delete my account and/or personal information?**

If you would like to delete your Latest Deals account and remove all personal data stored go to the [Contact Us page](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/contact) and select the reason 'Delete My Account'.

Please note that Facebook Messenger and WhatsApp notifications are not linked to your Latest Deals account. If you would like to unsubscribe please type "STOP" to the respective service.

 **Cookies**

We use cookies to save your preferences for viewing Latest Deals e.g. whether you want to view the homepage in a "list" view or "grid" view. We also use cookies for security reasons.

 **Third party websites**

We do not sell anything ourselves at Latest Deals - we are a community that links to deals and offers at various retailers (e.g. Amazon, Tesco or eBay). As these are third party websites not under our control we encourage you to check their privacy policy before providing any personal data. You can tell when you have left Latest Deals as the URL will no longer be [www.latestdeals.co.uk](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/).

 **Sharing deals & commenting**

If you share a deal or comment on our website then you are free - within reason - to say or do what you like. However, to be on the cautious side we would recommend that you avoid sharing any personal information. If you see something on our site that you're not happy about, drop us a line and we'll look into it for you.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

We may update this policy from time to time. We therefore recommend that you review this page periodically for any changes. Any such changes are effective as soon as they are published to this page.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy please [contact us](https://www.latestdeals.co.uk/contact) and we'll do our best to help.
